Audrey Crockett

Data Scientist

Location Saint Louis, MO

Phone (865) 228-9412

E-mail acrockett@syr.edu

LinkedIn audreymcrockett



Data Science master's graduate with 18 months experience working in radiation oncology bioinformatics, who would like to leverage her for experience as a social scientist and mental health therapist to communicate data outcomes effectively and assist clients with making data informed decisions.

Experience

| 2018 - present | Data Scientist <i>Radialogica, LLC</i> |
|----------------|--|
| 2016 - 2017 | Clinical Therapist Mosaic Community Services |
| 2015 - 2016 | Supervisor of Admissions Powell Recovery Center |
| 2013 - 2015 | Clinical Therapist Behavioral Health Partners of Frederick |
| 2011 - 2014 | Research Assistant Frostburg State University |

Education

| 2018 - 2019 | Syracuse University, Master's of Applied Data Science |
|-------------|--|
| 2011 - 2014 | Frostburg State University - Master's of Counseling Psychology |
| 2008 - 2010 | University of Tennessee - Bachelor's of Science - Psychology |

Skills



Research

- Edwards, J. H., Crockett, A. M., Miller, J., Tola, M., Zimonjic, N., & Hickman, D. (2014, August)

 Obesity and cardiovascular health risks in undergraduate college students. Poster presented at the 121st annual meeting of the American Psychological Association, Washington, D.C.
- Murtagh, M. P., Armiento, A. B., Kiddy, A. S., & Crockett, A. M. (2014, August). **Effectiveness of Frostburg State University's Sexual Assault Awareness Program.** Presented at the 121st annual meeting of the American Psychological Association, Washington, D.C.
- Murtagh, M. P., Hollingsworth, S. G., Crockett, A. M., & Murtagh, A. M. (2014, August). **Effects of abuse history on decisions to date.** Presented at the 121st annual meeting of the American Psychological Association, Washington, D.C.
- Edwards, J. H., Crockett, A. M., Miller, J., & Tola, M. (2014, March) College student's accuracy about health status: do gender and ethnicity matter? Poster presented at annual meeting of the Eastern Psychological Association, Boston, MA the 85th annual meeting of the Eastern Psychological Association, Boston, MA.
- Edwards, J. H., Crockett, A. M., Edwards, M. E. Miller, J., & Tola, M. (2013, March). College student's self-reported and actual health status. Poster presented at the 84th annual meeting of the Eastern Psychological Association, New York, NY.
- Crockett, A. M., Edwards, J. H., & Meisterjahn, R. (2013, March) **German and American student perspectives on disruptive behavior in the university classroom.** Poster presented at the 84th annual meeting of the Eastern Psychological Association, New York, NY.
- Edwards, J. H., Crockett, A. M. Zimonjic, N., & Hickman, D. (2012, March) College Student perspectives on keeping class interesting to prevent disruptive classroom behavior. Poster presented at the 83rd annual meeting of the Eastern Psychological Association, Pittsburg, PA.